Guide to the Hunter Ripley Rawlings papers, 1995-2006.
Rawlings, Hunter Ripley papers, 1995-2006
- Series II. Papers
  - CCC- LLC Policy Board, 1999-2000 (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - Physicians Organization History (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - Physicians Organization Policy Board, 2000-2001 (Box 114, Folder 36)
  - Resolution RE: Governance of Med. College and Graduate School of Medical Science, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - CUMC Campaign Case Statement, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 38)
  - Joan and Sanford I. Weill Medical College, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Joan and Sanford I. Weill Medical College Board of Overseers Business and Finance Committee (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Board of Overseers- Membership and Nominating Committee, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Joan and Sanford I. Weill Medical College, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Overseers Retreat, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 6-7)
  - CUMC Board of Overseers Agenda and Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - CUMC Board of Overseers Agenda and Minutes, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 9-10)
  - Investigation of Certain Tax Matters at Cornell University Medical College, 1995 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Hatfield Forum/Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Committee to Consider Applications for Support for R.S. Hatfield Fund for Economic Ed., 1980-1981 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Committee to Select Speaker for Cornell Corporate Forum, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Hays, Clark, 1993-1994, 1998-2001 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Hays, Clark, 1991, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Charles Feeney, 1997-2001 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Charles Feeney, 1993-1996 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Charles Feeney, 1991-1994 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Charles Feeney, August 1991 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Charles Feeney, March 26, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Charles Feeney, 1990-1991 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Feeney/Handlan/Dale, September 6, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Charles Feeney, 1989-1990 (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - Charles Feeney, April 17, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 25)
  - Charles Feeney, December 5, 1989 (Box 115, Folder 26)
  - Charles Feeney, 1988-1989 (Box 115, Folder 27)
  - Meeting in NYC with Feeney/Handlan/Dale/WKK Re: Alumni Admissions Center, April 11, 1989 2-4p.m. (Box 115, Folder 28)
  - Meeting with Charles Feeney- The Savoy, London, November 1, 1988 8:00a.m. (Box 115, Folder 29)
  - Charles Feeney, 1988 (Box 115, Folder 30)
  - Charles Feeney, 1986-1988 (Box 115, Folder 31)
  - Jane Foster, 1991-1993, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 32)
  - Hertzberg, 1986-1988 (Box 115, Folder 33)
  - Meeting with Benjamin and Lilian Hertzberg in N.Y.C., March 11, 1987 10:30a.m. (Box 115, Folder 34)
  - Meeting with Benjamin and Lilian Hertzberg, June 14, 1986 4:15-4:30p.m. (Box 115, Folder 35)
  - Hertzberg, 1985-1986 (Box 115, Folder 36)
  - Jewish Studies-Hertzberg, 1985-1986 (Box 115, Folder 37)
  - Ann Huntzinger, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 38)
  - Archives (Presidential Papers), 1969, 1972-1975, 1977, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 39)
  - Referrals List, 1975, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 40)
  - Academic Cabinet Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Accreditation Study- University, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - ACSW Meeting with President, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Committee- Provost's- Distance Learning, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Committee- Provost's- Internet Teaching, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action, Sexual Harassment and other statements, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Africana Center, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Alumni- PCCW, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Letters, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Alumni- Trustee Subcommittee on Distance Learning, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Arecibo, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Asia Strategy, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Assie-Lumumba, 1994-2000 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Assoc. Vice Provost for Statutory College Affairs, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Athletics and Physical Education, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Athletics Task Force Report, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Audit Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Bartels Fellowship, 1993-2001 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Bias Activity Response, Diversity and Inclusiveness, 1995-2001 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - Bias Incidents, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - BioGenomics Proposal, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - Biological Sciences, 1997-1998 (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - Biological Sciences, 1998-2000 (Box 104, Folder 24)
  - Biological Sciences, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 25-27)
  - Biology- Office of Undergraduate Biology, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 28)
  - Biomedical Research Alliance of Upstate New York, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 29)
  - Bursar's Office, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 30)
  - Campus Code, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 31)
  - Campus Safety- Lighting, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 32)
  - Center for International Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 33)
  - Center for International Studies, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 34)
  - Center for Teaching and Learning, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 35)
  - Christmas Card (Box 104, Folder 36)
  - Community Relations, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 37-38)
  - Community Relations- City of Ithaca and Cornell Memo of Understanding, 1990-1995 (Box 104, Folder 39)
  - Community Relations- Music Festival Initiative with Ithaca, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 40)
  - Civic Engagement and Service Learning, 2000 (Box 116, Folder 1-2)
  - Controller's Office, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Abroad, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Cornell China Scholars Program, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Chronicle (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Cornell in the News, 1990s (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Cornell in the News, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Cornell/SUNY Relationship, 1995-1996 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Cornell United Religious Work (CURW)- Director's Search, 2000 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Auditor, 1996-2000 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence- Bartels, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- Bovays, 2000 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- Craft, Hal, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- Dean of Students, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- Desai, Ravi, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- Field, Bill; Rusten, Jeff- Classics Gift, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- Foremost Benefactors, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- Hyman, Jay (Esbaran Agreement), 2001 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- Johnson, Rev. Robert, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence- Kheel, Ted- Biodiversity Program, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence and Memos- Martin, Biddy, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- Merrill, Phillip, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence- Milstein, Howard, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence-Morgan, Rebecca and James, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence- Presidential Councillor, 1980-2000 (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence- Presidential Councillor, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence and Memos- Rawlings, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence- Schwartz, Richard and Sheila, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence- Tanners, 1998-2001 (Box 116, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence- Vice President for Student Affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 32)
  - Computing and Information Sciences, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 33)
  - Computing and Information Sciences, 1999-2000 (Box 116, Folder 34)
  - Designated Spokesperson for Issues, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 35)
  - Executive Staff Photo, 1990; 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 36)
  - Computing and Information Sciences, 1998-1999 (Box 116, Folder 37)
  - Corning Site Visit, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 38)
  - Critical Maintenance, 2000 (Box 116, Folder 39)
  - Decennial Reaccreditation Self-Study Process, 1999-2000 (Box 116, Folder 40)
  - Department Chairs Program, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 41)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 42)
  - Department of Justice- Antitrust Consent Decree, 1993-1994 (Box 116, Folder 43)
  - Dissection, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 44)
  - Distance Learning, 1998-1999 (Box 116, Folder 45-50)
  - Distance Learning- Report to the Provost, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 51)
  - Distance Learning Task Force, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 52)
  - Duel Career Challenge, 2000 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Duffield Hall, 1999-2000 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - e-Cornell, 1999-2000 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - e-Cornell, 2000-2001 (Box 117, Folder 4-19)
  - East Asian Studies, 2001 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Emergency Preparedness Plan, 1999 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Environmental Health, 2000-2001 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Environmental Statement, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Seminars Proposal, 1999 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Relations, 2000-2001 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Francille Firebaugh General, 2000-2001 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Francille Firebaugh General, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Francille Firebaugh General, 2000 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 2000-2001 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Freshman Resource Center, 2000 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Fuller Professorship, 2001 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Gender and Global Change, 1999 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - Genomics Initiative, 2000-2001 (Box 117, Folder 33-35)
  - Genomics Initiative, 1999-2000 (Box 117, Folder 36)
  - Genomics Initiative- transparencies (Box 117, Folder 37)
  - Golf Course Remodel, 2001 (Box 117, Folder 38)
  - Health Services, 2000-2001 (Box 117, Folder 39)
  - Higher Education Opportunity Program, 2000 (Box 117, Folder 40)
  - Hillel, 1997-1998 (Box 117, Folder 41)
  - Institute for Biotechnology and Life Science Technologies, 2000 (Box 117, Folder 42)
  - International Studies, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - International Studies, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - International Studies, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Inventory of silverware, dishes, linens in the A.D. White Museum, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Y2K- Life Sci. Tech Building For Genomics, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Kendal, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Kushner Yeshiva High School, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - KYOTO Flap, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - KYOTO Flap (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - KYOTO Flap (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Lab of Ornithology, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Lake Source Cooling, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Leadership Development Feedback, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Ludwig Institute for Cancer Research, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Minority Education- American Indian Program, 1999-2001 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Mission Statement, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - MIT Meeting- Gender Equity, 1999-2001 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Mouse Facilities, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Nanobiotechnology Center, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Newman Lab, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - NCAA, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - NYS Office of Science, Technology and Academic Research, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - NYSTAR (NYS Office of Science Technology and Academic Research), 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - NYSTAR (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Open Meeting Guidelines, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - Parents Letter, 1995-2000 (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - Payson House- NYC, 1979-1999 (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - Phoenix Plan, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - Planning and Facilities, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 29-30)
  - Policy on Acceptance of Gifts, 1972-1978 (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - Policy on the Formulation of University Policies, 1993 (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - Policy on Unscheduled Events, 1972,1978,1984 (Box 118, Folder 33)
  - Policy Revisions, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 34)
  - Presidential Research Scholars, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 35)
  - President's House- 511 Cayuga Heights Road, 1995-2000 (Box 118, Folder 36)
  - Public Service/ Community Development (FF), 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 37)
  - Real Estate, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 38)
  - Regulations for the Maintenance of Public Order (RMPO), 1986 (Box 118, Folder 39)
  - Regulations Concerning Demonstrations Inside University Buildings, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 40)
  - Report of Commission to Review Campus Judicial System, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 41)
  - Reports of Educational Issues- Prof. Robert Cooke, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 42)
  - Presidential Initiative Status Reports, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 43)
  - Presidential Initiative Status Reports, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 44)
  - "Retention Issues Among Members of Groups Under-represented on the Cornell Faculty", April 26, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 45)
  - Senior Faculty Seminar Proposal, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 46)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy, 1996-1997 (Box 118, Folder 47)
  - Singapore Strategies Alliance, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 48)
  - Slope Day Letter, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 49)
  - State Relations, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 50)
  - Statement of University's Values, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Statement of Symbolic Structures, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Summaries of Research/ Public Service Programs, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Telephone Switch Decision, 2000 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Transaction Authority, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Trustee Employee and Labor Relations Policy, 1970-2000 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Education- Ethics Courses, Business Education, 1999-2001 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - US News and World Report Rankings, 1996-2001 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - University Council, 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - University Police, 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - University-Wide Policy Statement and Communications, 1998 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Vice President of University Relations, 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Vice President's Group, 1997-2000 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Wari House, 2001-2002 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - West Campus Housing, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - West Campus Living Learning Council, 2000 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Working Together Memo, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Salaries, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 1A)
  - FAC Senate: Principles on Cooperation and Consultation, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 1B)
  - Financial Policy Committee, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 1C)
  - FAC Salaries: 9 month comparison to peer group, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 1D)
  - FAC Salaries 2000, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 1E)
  - Faculty Salaries supporting material from 4/13 meeting with Arts and Sciences faculty, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 1F)
  - Teaching Quality #1, 1996 (Box 120, Folder 2A)
  - Off Campus Learning Teaching Activities, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 2B)
  - Faculty Recognition Draft Letters Provost Randel, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 2C)
  - Indemnification Policy, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 2D)
  - Commencement, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 3A)
  - Commencement Coordinator, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 3B)
  - Redesign and Repair of Barton Hall Sound System, 1976 (Box 120, Folder 3C)
  - Timetable for Commencement (During Year), 1977 (Box 120, Folder 3D)
  - Honorary Degree Letter, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 3E)
  - Procedure for Selection of New University Marshall, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 3F)
  - Commencement, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 3G)
  - Joy Wagner Mace Bearer (Box 120, Folder 3H)
  - Department of Education, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Glee Club, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Higher Education-General, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 6A)
  - Doonesbury (Box 120, Folder 6B)
  - National Cost Commission Recommendations, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 6C)
  - NYS Attorney General Opinion on Regents Right, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 6D)
  - "The Public Interest" Derek Bok, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 6E)
  - Higher Education Bundy Money, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Morrill Act Higher Education- Miscellaneous Bills (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Background Papers Institutional Neutrality, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Higher Education Miscellaneous Papers, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 10A)
  - Carson Report, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 10B)
  - University President's Statements on CAW, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 10C)
  - Higher Education State Education Department, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 11A)
  - State Ed- Contract, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 11B)
  - State Ed. Original Signed, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 11C)
  - Ujamaa, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - SUNY, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 13A)
  - Brookhaven, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 13B)
  - Albany, October 18, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 13C)
  - SUNY, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 13D-E)
  - SUNY Cornell Rec., 1998 (Box 120, Folder 13F)
  - SUNY Principles of Affiliation Agreement, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 13G)
  - AAU, April-June 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1A)
  - AAU Spring International Convention, April 22-24, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1B pt.1-2)
  - AAU Exec-Comm, April 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1C pt.1-2)
  - Sam Johnson, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 2A)
  - Sam Johnson, August 15, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 2B)
  - Sam Johnson, June 10, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 2C)
  - Sam Johnson Visit, September 14, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 2D)
  - Sam Johnson, March 23, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 2E)
  - Sam Johnson, March 25, 1993 (Box 121, Folder 2F)
  - Sam Johnson, November 1992 (Box 121, Folder 2G)
  - MCN/RMR Meeting, December 7, 1992 (Box 121, Folder 2H)
  - Sam Johnson, July-November 1992 (Box 121, Folder 2I)
  - Sam Johnson, July 16, 1992 (Box 121, Folder 2J)
  - Faculty Preference for Johnson Facility, 1991 (Box 121, Folder 2K)
  - Sam Johnson, September-December 1991 (Box 121, Folder 2L)
  - Sam Johnson, September 19, 1991 (Box 121, Folder 2M)
  - Sam Johnson/Austin Kiplinger, November 7, 1991 (Box 121, Folder 2N)
  - Charles Knight, 1998 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Lester Knight, September 2000 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Charles Lake, 2000 (Box 121, Folder 5A)
  - Charles and Louise Lake, July 15, 1992 (Box 121, Folder 5B)
  - Charles Lake, December 1991 (Box 121, Folder 5C)
  - F. Newman, January 1993 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Jansen Noyes, May 1996 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Spencer Olin, October-November 1996 (Box 121, Folder 8A)
  - Spencer Olin Funeral Service, April 18, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 8B)
  - Spencer Olin, January-June 1995 (Box 121, Folder 8C)
  - Nathaniel A. Owings, January 1987 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Purcell, February 2001 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Snee, June 1994 (Box 121, Folder 11A)
  - Katherine Snee, October 18, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 11B)
  - Snee, December 1993 (Box 121, Folder 11C)
  - Uris, September 2000 (Box 121, Folder 12A)
  - Ruth Uris, January 26, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 12B)
  - Uris, June 1994 (Box 121, Folder 12C)
  - Lunch With Ruth Uris, November 18, 1991 (Box 121, Folder 12D)
  - Ruth Uris Luncheon, October 14, 1991 (Box 121, Folder 12E)
  - Sandy Weill, April 2001 (Box 121, Folder 13A)
  - Meeting with Weill/Tanner, October 31, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 13B)
  - Sandy Weill, 1992 & 1996 (Box 121, Folder 13C)
  - Weill Gift Correspondence and photograph, April-June 1998 (Box 121, Folder 13D)
  - Stephen Weiss, February 2001 (Box 121, Folder 14 pt.1-2)
  - NAF Membership Files, November 29, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - DMR Memo to DDD re: Admissions and F/A Reorganization, March 17, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Racial and Sexual Harassment, January 1987 (Box 121, Folder 17A)
  - Racism at CU (Simba Wachanga), October 30, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 17B)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 1A-D)
  - Service and Maintenance, March 28, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Rawling's Priorities, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 2A)
  - Call to Serve, January 28, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Fraternity and Sorority Council, April 14, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Cornell in Qatar, October 12, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Integrated Pest Management, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - The Jerusalem Report, April 5, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Sebastien Marot, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Cayuga Addiction Recovery Services, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Reflection in Action, January 8, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Army ROTC Information Kit, January 8, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, November 30, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Mellon Humanities Seminar Readings, December 5, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2000 & 2001 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Meeting with Sandy Weill, December 5, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Hong Kong, Taiwan, and Japan, December 4, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - 2001 Holiday Reception Response List, December 4, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - CUSS, December 4, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Rawling's Plane Ticket, December 4, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Harel Weinstein, December 4, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Nominations and Governance Committee, December 1, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - Haverford College, November 8, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 23)
  - Meeting of the Academic Cabinet, December 3, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 24)
  - Appointment for Samuel Lucas, November 21, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - HP Meeting Confirmation, November 26, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 26)
  - Time with HRR, November 19, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, December 10, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 28)
  - Joseph P. Frey, December 4, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 29)
  - Samuel O. Thier, December 4, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 30)
  - Ambassador Loucas Tsilas, December 10, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 31)
  - Arthur Wolcott, December 10, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 32)
  - Early Admissions, December 10, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 33)
  - Bill Clinton, December 10, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 34)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, December 6, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 35)
  - Edwin L. Eaton, December 11, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 36)
  - Winston Lo, December 11, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 37)
  - SUNY, December 7, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, December 10, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 39)
  - Evan Stewart, December 10, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 40)
  - George E. Pataki, December 11, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 41)
  - Richard A. Baker, December 13, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 42)
  - NCAA, December 13, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 43)
  - Joshua Goldman, December 13, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 44)
  - AAU, October 20, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 45)
  - White Hall Tour, September 5, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 46)
  - Meeting, October 8, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 47)
  - October Dates, February 26, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 48)
  - Lab of Ornithology Administrative Board Dinner, October 17, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 49)
  - Student Athlete, September 23, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 50)
  - Senior Staff Meeting, October 16, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 51)
  - Montpellier, October 10, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 52)
  - Ed Reinfurt Visit, October 10, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 53)
  - Tenure Faculty Reception, October 16, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 54)
  - Salute to newly tenured faculty, May 25, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 54)
  - President Address to Employees, June 19, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 55)
  - Harry Bovay/HRR, October 10, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 56)
  - Cornell's Adult University, September 27, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 57)
  - West Campus Council, September 23, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 58)
  - Dinner with Irwin Jacobs, October 10, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 59)
  - Meeting with Caryl and Mickey Hart, October 8, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 60)
  - Meeting of the Academic Cabinet, October 7, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 61)
  - Meeting with Michael Zak, September 19, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 62)
  - AAU Humanities Task Force, September 10, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 63)
  - Capital Funding and Priorities Committee Schedule, March 26, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 64)
  - Qatar, September 11, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 65)
  - Nominations and Governance Committee, October 5, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 66)
  - Haverford College, September 3, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 67)
  - Tri-Institutional Research Program, October 2, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 68)
  - Tech Park Presidents Lunch, September 30, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 69)
  - AAU Humanities Task Force, September 10, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 70)
  - Tri-Institutional Faculty Procedures, September 17, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 71)